I used to believe
We were burnin′ on the edge
of somethin′ beautiful
Somethin′ beautiful
Sellin′ a dream
Smoke and mirrors keep us
waiting on a miracle
On a miracle
Say‚ go through the darkest of days
Heaven′s a heartbreak away
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Oh‚ It is been a hell of a ride
Driving the edge of a knife
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you
Don′t fall asleep
At the whel‚ we′ve got a million
miles ahead of us
Miles ahead of us
All that we need
Is a rude awakening to know
We are good enough
Know We are good enough
Say go through the darkest of days
Heaven′s a heartbreak away
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Oh‚ It is been a hell of a ride
Driving the edge of a knife
Never let you go‚ never let me down
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you
Don′t you give up‚ nah nah nah
I won′t give up‚ nah nah nah
Let me love you
www.RentAnAdviser.com