By RentAnAdviser.com
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh duh
This hit
That ice cold
Michelle Pfeiffer
That white gold
This one for them hood girls
Them good girls
Straight masterpieces
Stylin′‚ wilin
Livin′ in up in the city
Got chucks on with Saint Laurent
Gotta kiss myself I am so pretty
I am too hot (hot damn)
Call the po lice and the fireman
Make a dragon wanna retire‚ man
I am too hot (hot damn)
Say my name you know who I am
And my band ′bout that money
Break it down
Girls hit your hallelujah
′Cause Uptown Funk gon′ give it to ya
Saturday night and we in the spot
Don′t believe me just watch (Come on)
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Don′t believe me just watch
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Don′t believe me just watch
Hey‚ hey‚ hey‚ oh!
Stop
Wait a minute
Fill my cup put some liquor in it
Take a sip‚ sign a check
Julio‚ Get the stretch!
Ride to Harlem‚ Hollywood‚
Jackson‚ Mississippi
If we show up‚ we gon′ show out
Smoother than a fresh jar of Skippy
I am too hot (hot damn)
Call the po lice and the fireman
Make a dragon wanna retire‚ man
I am too hot (hot damn) hot damn
Bitch‚ say my name you know who I am
I am too hot (hot damn)
And my band ′bout that money
Break it down
Girls hit your hallelujah
′Cause Uptown Funk gon′ give it to ya
Saturday night and we in the spot
Don′t believe me just watch (come on)
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Don′t believe me just watch
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Don′t believe me just watch
Hey‚ hey‚ hey‚ oh!
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Before we leave
Let me tell y′all a le something
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown Funk you up
I said Uptown Funk you up‚
Uptown Funk you up
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown Funk you up
Come on‚ dance
Jump on it
If you sexy then flaunt it
If you freaky then own it
Don′t brag about it‚ come show me
Come on‚ dance
Jump on it
If you sexy then flaunt it
Well It is Saturday night
and we in the spot
Don′t believe me just watch (come on)
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Don′t believe me just watch
Doh
Doh doh doh‚ doh doh doh‚ doh doh
Don′t believe me just watch
Hey‚ hey‚ hey‚ oh!
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown
Funk you up (say whaa?)
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown Funk you up
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown
Funk you up (say whaa?)
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown Funk you up
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown
Funk you up (say whaa?)
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown Funk you up
Uptown Funk you up‚ Uptown
Funk you up (say whaa?)
Uptown Funk you up
aaow!
By RentAnAdviser.com